{
    "subject": "resource/Murata_Manufacturing",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Murata Manufacturing Company, Ltd.",
    "human_readable": "The name of Murata Manufacturing is Murata Manufacturing Company, Ltd.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9778566956520081,
            "question": "Is 'Murata Manufacturing' the official name of the company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9631537795066833,
            "question": "What type of company is Murata Manufacturing Company, Ltd.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9373544454574585,
            "question": "What is the full name of Murata Manufacturing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9201249480247498,
            "question": "Where is Murata Manufacturing Company, Ltd. headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8957156538963318,
            "question": "When was Murata Manufacturing Company, Ltd. founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8257753849029541,
            "question": "What industry does Murata Manufacturing operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7615832686424255,
            "question": "Does Murata Manufacturing have any subsidiaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7349135875701904,
            "question": "What products or services does Murata Manufacturing offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6839196681976318,
            "question": "What is Murata Manufacturing's mission statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6179752945899963,
            "question": "Who are the key executives at Murata Manufacturing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Murata Manufacturing is Murata Manufacturing Company, Ltd.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1257_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Murata Manufacturing's mission statement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1257_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What products or services does Murata Manufacturing offer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1257_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Murata Manufacturing have any subsidiaries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1257_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1257_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\nThe provided documents contain information about the company Murata Manufacturing Co., Ltd. and do not contradict the statement that its full official name is \"Murata Manufacturing Company, Ltd.\" Thus, according to the given context, the answer is 'yes'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Murata Manufacturing is not referred to as a \"Company\" in the provided context. It is identified as a \"Co., Ltd.\" which stands for Kabushiki Kaisha, a type of corporation used primarily in Japan.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}